What is going on, Dhruv?
I can tell from your body language
that you are simply not interested.
I love your enthusiasm, Kavya.
It's almost contagious.
Look, Dhruv, you're smart,
you're intelligent,
but you have no motivation left.
Do you really want to work here?
Honestly, the way your work
has improved is truly commendable.
Look, your mind is clearly somewhere else.
Don't you think it's time to just move on?
Are you ready to start managing a team?
I know you will do really well.
So now what, like...
I don't have to come from tomorrow?
So, when do I take on the new role?
-Hello.
-I want to tell you something!
Yes, even I want to tell you something.
I got a promotion and a raise!
-What?
-A fucking promotion and a--
Okay. Congrats, congrats.
By the way,
Yohan is throwing a party at his house.
It's a house warming. Be there by 7. Okay?
What did you want to tell?
I found a guy selling dumplings.
Calls himself Taste of Darjeeling.
It's very good.
We should come here, you know.
-It's very good.
-Dhruv, you are so cute, dude.
You eat them. Have some on me.
-Today is a very happy day.
-Yeah.
-See you. Love you.
-Yeah. Happy day.
Give me some more, buddy.
Hi.
Please, take some more.
-Hi, Pizza Mania.
-Actually, I'm Dhruv.
-Dhruv?
-Kavya's boyfriend.
Pizza Mania.
-Dhruv, how are you?
-Yohan.
-I'm good. How are you?
-Very good.
-I'll get it.
-No, I'll do it.
-No, it's fine.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
-Okay, thank you.
-You don't mind?
-No.
Please, come in. Thank you so much.
It's a beautiful house.
-Thank you.
-Give me some.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah, yeah.
Is it uncomfortable?
Yeah.
-Hi!
-Congratulations.
Thank you. Dhruv!
-Are you drunk?
-No.
I'm very happy.
Twenty two lakhs per annum.
What are you serious? Twenty two?
-What the fuck?
-I know.
-Now you can buy everything.
-I'll buy a factory.
-Shut up!
-Listen, dude.
We should go to Moonlight to celebrate.
It's okay to celebrate with
other people sometimes.
Come, I'll show you the house.
-Hello.
-Wow, how are you doing?
-Good, dude.
-Good, man.
-You got pizza?
-Yes, let's go have some.
Let's go.
-Super unsure about it.
-About what?
It's too much.
I'm really bored with everything.
I'm bored with Tinder, my job sucks,
I'm bored with Zomato,
and even looking at pizza
makes me feel fat.
The final season of "Girls" is over and...
Look, if you are not happy,
you should quit.
Find something else.
It's better than being unhappy every day.
Yeah, she's right.
So, are you looking forward
to being in Bombay?
Yes, we very well should.
As in?
We've actually bought this house.
You bought a house in Bombay,
and a house like this!
-Really?
-It's nice, no?
-It's great!
-Thanks. And what do you do?
-I teach math online.
-Something like that exists?
Yeah, very much.
He's also a data analyst at a startup.
And what happened to the PhD?
-He's actually doing his PhD in math.
-Yeah, so I was, but I quit.
Yeah. But eventually
he might just get back to it.
I don't know about that, but... let's see.
I wasn't having fun.
It's really as simple as that.
Talk about not having fun.
I actually have to be a housewife
for 49 days.
Some kind of traditional ritual thing,
I tell you.
Is it really that bad?
You're staying at home,
you're doing work
and you're managing the house.
It's nice, right?
I wouldn't mind doing it.
Yes, but that's the difference, right?
When you choose to do it
versus when you are forced to do it.
Yes, fair point.
I kind of agree with Dhruv.
Who wouldn't want to sit at home
and take care of the house? Or just chill?
-Really?
-No?
Then you stay at home for 49 days.
-Chill.
-You can work if you want to.
I've just told her
not to post any pictures
on any of those social media sites.
That's it.
That's going to be difficult.
Anyway, we'll just got meet
a few other people.
-Yes, you please carry on.
-Have another drink.
-Help yourselves.
-See you.
See you.
Shut up.
Is this dessert?
Smells like it.
Be careful. It's not your dad's.
What?
Smell. It's dessert, right?
Sweet. It's not dessert. It's nice.
It smells like dessert.
Can you imagine he bought this house?
I know. People have so much money.
He must have planned it well.
It's not easily done.
Dude, how much could he have planned?
He's a CEO, right?
He's not a CEO, he's a bastard.
-Dhruv.
-What? He is a bastard, right?
The jerk has cheated on her.
Can you imagine?
It's their personal shit.
They'll figure it out on their own.
Yeah, but still!
The same office. Doesn't that feel weird?
This is my money also, no?
I mean, we're working as a team.
I'm just telling you to ask me
before you spend our money. That's it.
I won't say no, dude.
Yes, it is our money.
And I've kept all the records of it.
What's yours is yours.
If you want,
I can send you the document right away.
Do you want me to mail it to you, huh?
It feels awesome.
-Let me be their servant.
-Wow.
How ambitious!!
At least say "caretaker" or "manager."
Caretakers are also servants.
You]re in this bathroom,
that's why you're speaking English.
Same shit.
Did you talk to the sister about the gift?
No.
How do I say it to her?
It should come from her, no?
I mean, she knows that
the down payment is due.
Maybe she's forgotten.
Why don't you just remind her?
God, this is so tiring, dude.
We forgot to give them
a house warming gift.
No. Wait. I have it.
I have a two-day old cardamom.
Where has it gone?
-Dhruv.
-Where is it?
-It's okay. I have a better plan.
-Tissue.
I have Lonely Planet Mumbai in my bag,
we gift her that and we can write
all the stuff we love to do in the city
and places we love to go to.
That's actually nice.
-Isn't it? It'll be like our guide.
-Yeah. That's sweet.
It's not your dad's.
Take care of everything, Cherry.
And from now on,
absolute transparency.
Complete transparency, I promise.
Yes?
Yes, it's my car.
What is the matter?
Yes, it's our flat.
It's not a rental. Yes.
Extra for parking?
I won't give you any money at all, sir.
Because you guys think
we're fucking morons!
What?
Eight hundred thousand rupees, dude.
For parking. Bloody hell!
Listen.
I love you, okay?
I love you, too.
Shall we go?
Otherwise the appetizers
will be all gone.
Let's go.
They must have had sex.
What can you say?
So, do you think
Salman Khan is a virgin?
What the fuck?
You really think that he's a virgin?
-It's okay. I'm just asking.
-No, he's not.
Why does everybody think
Salman Khan is a virgin?
-I like him.
-So that doesn't make him a virgin.
God!
Salman Khan a virgin?
What the hell?
How much rent
do you and Kavya pay together?
Why, you planning to shift?
-I'm bored of my place.
-That doesn't mean you're going to shift.
-Istanbul is Turkey's capital, right?
-Yeah.
-Ankara.
-It's Istanbul.
-No, Istanbul.
-Ankara.
-Yes, I just won 220 bucks.
-See?
-What? Was it Istanbul or Ankara?
-Ankara. Thank you.
-Since when did it become Ankara?
-These guys had sex, too.
-You guys good?
You know, for girls like us,
who belong to middle class
or upper middle class backgrounds,
it feels so nice, right?
You don't have to rely on a boyfriend,
or family for your needs.
You don't have to.
It's not like
we're chasing money or anything.
We just want to be self sustainable.
I want to be self sustainable.
I mean, tomorrow if I go to a store
and I spot a pair of shoes
that I really want to buy,
-then I should be able to buy it.
-Right.
It makes you feel so nice,
it makes you feel so empowered,
because you are saving.
Most of our mothers did not have
these experiences.
-Right?
-Right.
And on top of that, if you enjoy your job,
then it's the best. It's the best feeling.
-And our parents feel so relieved.
-Not just relieved. They are happy
they are proud of us.
-Show me.
-Show me yours.
What? Man, what a camera.
How much was it? It's great.
-It's free for you, brother-in-law.
-I'm not kidding. Tell me.
Not yet. We wanna take pictures first.
Where is Kavya? Have you seen her?
What are you doing? Shopping?
-What's the matter?
-Look at this. This website.
It calculates the time
you spend with the family
-when you are living away from them.
-Okay.
Let's say you live in a city,
and your parents live in another,
you meet them three, four,
let's say five times a year.
They average that out.
According to them, I will see my parents
for like now 321 days.
321 times.
For the rest of my life before they die.
-That's like one year.
Understand this, till now
I've seen them every day of my life.
Like, till I was 20 years old.
Now, in my remaining 30,
40, or 50 years,
I will be with them just for one year.
We're fucking morons.
I'm selling light bulbs.
Why am I doing this?
Why am I so far away from them?
Check it out.
No, thanks. It's too depressing.
Such a nice finish, huh?
What an awesome house.
-Open the fridge.
-Open it.
Dude, I want to buy
a fridge for my parents.
Which one do I buy?
You're buying a fridge for your parents?
That's quite amazing.
As a kid, ten seemed a lot,
now 10,000 doesn't seem enough.
Right. I feel like that time was better.
Little is best.
What a privileged statement.
No, dude, "little" is not the right word.
-Simple is the right word, right?
-Yeah, right.
Simple is best.
Like trousers.
Wow, expensive cheese, huh?
-Where did you get it from?
-From the fridge.
-What?
-Seriously?
-From the fridge--
-You guys are shameless.
Kavya, he will demote you.
It's delicious. Try it.
Yes, I'll eat some, too.
What are you guys doing here?
And where are your drinks?
-Out there.
-Yes, outside.
-Lovely kitchen.
-Great kitchen.
Thank you.
It's great fun cooking over here.
-We should do a pot luck some day.
-Yeah.
-It's a great idea.
-It's a beautiful house, too.
Thank you. Me and Cherry just love it.
It's superb.
-Oh, boy. Not again.
-God.
Just give me a second, I'll figure it out.
Guys, just be careful. Please.
Just be careful.
Really sorry about this.
We'll just figure it out. Just be careful.
Guys.
Cherry?
What are you doing here?
Everyone is waiting outside.
-What are you looking at?
-Can't you see?
What?
What the fuck have we gotten into?
What are you thinking?
I quit my job.
I don't know. I don't know
whether they fired me or not, but...
What?
Really?
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm okay.
I was just scared to tell you
because you were having such a great day.
I was scared
that I'd ruin it or something.
We're a team, Dhruv.
Why will I be upset? I'm sure
you'll figure something out.
Want water?
-Sure? We can stop.
-Come here, baby.
Thank you.
What are you thinking?
Listen.
I quit my job. Or they fired me,
I still don't know.
What? When?
This morning.
And you didn't think it was important to
talk to me about it or discuss it with me?
Wait. Dude, it just happened.
Okay.
-Okay?
-Yes, okay.
What do you mean by, "Yes, okay"?
Say something more.
I'm just trying to process
this information right now, Dhruv.
Give me time.
What happened? Will you share the details?
Nothing. They figured
I am not happy there.
I'm not enjoying work. So they gave me
an option and I chose to quit. Simple.
So they didn't fire you,
you chose to quit?
Yes. That's what happened.
I feel better now, suddenly, about it.
Screw feeling better, Dhruv!
You took such a big step
without even involving me in it!
Wait. You knew that I wasn't happy there.
Then you told about your promotion,
I thought you'll take care of the house,
I can chill for a bit.
Chill?
I know it's your decision, Dhruv,
and I know it's your life,
but you should have at least spoken to me.
We would have talked this through.
-It affects the both of us, Dhruv.
-Wait.
-Yes, but--
-You should not have quit like that.
Wait! Why not?
It's my decision, no?
Why aren't you asking me,
"Dhruv, are you happy or not?"
It was my decision, dude.
Dhruv, this is
a very irresponsible decision.
Dude, don't do that
irresponsible shit again, man!
Enough with it.
Repeating the same thing.
I didn't like it, I quit.
-The topic is over, finished.
-You are irresponsible, Dhruv.
Can't you admit it for once?
-You can't even fix the shower.
-Why do you keep saying that
I asked, the problem is not at our end.
It's the building's problem.
What should I do?
-Climb the pipe and fix it?
-You think they'll fix it?
Get it done. Do I have to take care
of it myself?
Kavya, why are you talking like this?
Listen to yourself.
You're sounding so rude. If this is how
you want to talk, then don't talk.
It's funny you're talking like this.
Remember how considerate I was
when you wanted to quit?
Dhruv, that was long time ago, okay?
Things have changed now.
How have they changed?
Aren't you realizing we're growing up now?
So we continue to grow up
irrespective of--
No! I want to grow up
in a particular direction.
Exactly. Which is why I quit.
Dhruv, when I wanted to quit,
I spoke to you about it.
That's where I'm coming from, okay?
You should have discussed this with me.
What would be the use of that? My decision
would still have been the same.
Wow. Thanks, dude,
for making me feel important.
In that case,
you shouldn't even have told me.
Why tell me? What difference does it make?
And how are you going to pay
your parents' loan?
You don't want to take money from me.
I don't even know
what you want to do anymore, Dhruv.
Your money is your money.
My money is my money.
You can pay it back when you have some.
You want me to take another loan?
I will die!
-You're realizing that now?
-Why are you talking like this?
Then don't give it back, it's okay.
What are you doing?
You are really mind fucking me now.
Dhruv, I'm just trying to help you, okay?
You should have at least...
I mean, I'm your girlfriend, Dhruv!
I don't even know
what you want to do anymore.
You're just quitting everything. I mean...
Are you even understanding
that it affects the two of us?
It's the two of us now.
Why are you pressuring me?
Kavya, why aren't you asking me,
"Dhruv, are you okay?
"Are you feeling okay?"
Why aren't you saying,
"We'll figure it out,
we're a team,
let's work it out together."
Why aren't you saying things like that?
What did you tell Akshara at the party?
If your heart is not in it,
then don't do it!
That's what I did.
Isn't it the same thing?
-It's not the same, Dhruv.
-How is it not the same?
Because my life does not depend
on Akshara, it depends on you.
Bro, it doesn't depend on me.
You make enough money.
So it's not about that. Stop cribbing.
That's not the dependency
I'm talking about, you know that.
I'm not cribbing,
I'm just concerned about you.
How are you concerned?
You're making me feel so shitty.
What? You don't even value my opinion,
you don't involve me
in big decisions that you take.
Dude, you knew about this!
Anyway, it's...
I'll work this out. I'll manage myself,
-I'll manage the house. Don't worry.
-That's not what I meant.
I'm sorry I looked out for your future.
You worry about yours,
I'll worry about mine, and we'll be fine.
I just said that
because I was happy, okay?
And then you said this
and it ruined whatever--
See? This is what it's about.
That I fucking ruined your day, no?
Did I ruin your day? Yes, I did!
That's not what I meant.
-Dude, you just said that!
-That's not what I meant!
But you said it, no? That's what
you said. That I ruined your day.
How? By telling you I fucking quit?
Enough already!
Subtitle Translation by Neeti Ray