Sorry, sorry, sorry. Please continue.
Next to the medical store.
The medical store.
It's Axis Bank that's there, not ICICI.
Please, follow the location.
Okay, anyways, let's brainstorm
when we meet next.
Sure. Next week?
No, I'm afraid that's too far out.
Let's meet day after.
Day after would be too early for us.
I don't think we will be able to...
I understand, but we really need
to get something soon.
Anyway, other designers we spoke to
highly recommended you, so you know...
Yeah. Yeah, I understand.
We'll try and manage something.
I'm sure you will. Bye. See you.
Looking forward to it. Bye.
You wait there and I'll walk there.
Let's go. We have to walk for a bit.
-You should have called him here.
-I tried, dude.
-Today we have to work a bit longer.
-Why?
-We're presenting to them tomorrow.
-What? No!
-I'll just take a little bit.
-Yes, it's done.
-This is very tasty.
-What did you bring?
Tuna sandwich. You want a bite?
-What?
-Tuna.
Yuck, fish! How did you get it
in your bag? Doesn't it stink?
Stink? Tuna smells just like
your mashed vegetables.
-Do mashed vegetables smell?
-No, no. Sir, I'm giving an example.
Man, let me listen. You made me miss yoga!
How do we go back?
And what was he saying?
I saw it right away. You are from Delhi.
From where in Delhi, man?
-Rohini, dude.
-What are you saying?
-You, too? Wow.
-And this station, Kaushambi.
-This too falls in Delhi. NCR.
-Yes, bro.
This man, he can't digest his food
till he cracks the same joke 100 times.
After teaching, I need to do something.
Do you want me to teach the whole day?
A guy needs to breathe.
Why are you here? For the money?
Yes. No. I mean...
Yes, man, for the money.
What happened is I quit my job.
There is pressure at home.
I've already taken a loan, so...
I thought I'd try it out.
Whatever helps. You know, why not?
Like that.
You mean, like that?
-What?
-Yes, I mean,
he's from our area, we can tell him,
there is no problem.
-What happened?
-Bro, I'll sort our your money problem.
-Have you heard of IOS?
-Indian Open School.
Wow. You're both smart.
Here's the deal, they get students
who don't want to answer exams,
but want the degree.
Like Munna Bhai.
-You've seen Munna Bhai, right?
-Yes, I have.
But what are you guys trying to say?
-Institutes like ours have teachers.
-Yes.
But they answer the exams
for such students.
And these students give money in return.
And some students are so good,
they give 30, 000 to 40,000.
30,000 to 40,000? Motherfucker!
-No, what?
-Our Delhi boy.
No, no. Three...
30,000 to 40,000 for one exam?
Bro, 30,000 to 40,000 is
minimum guaranteed, did you know that?
Usually it's more than that.
And if you know someone
and recommend him to answer an exam,
you get an extra 15% as commission.
But, wait. So...
-How does it work out?
-Bro, it's not work.
There are Whatsapp groups
with IIT and BITS students.
The client sends a message.
And after that you go there.
-All right.
-Like we did.
Was it Bangalore? We went to Bangalore.
It's a lot of fun. It's very high.
Think about it carefully
and then let us know.
Yes, but...
-is it safe?
-Motherfucker, it's totally safe.
There's no problem at all.
You don't have to do anything.
You show up,
answer the exam for two hours,
-and leave.
-And let me tell you,
there are very few seats.
Forget about your commission,
I won't even get mine. Okay? Come.
-Okay?
-You guys go. My class is over.
-Okay. Let's go. All right.
-Let's go.
How much do you want?
What do you mean? We get equal shares.
This is not how it's done.
No, dude, Kavya. It doesn't work this way.
-Dude, this is not going to happen.
-Guys, relax.
We'll try. If it doesn't happen,
it doesn't happen. It's fine.
-Why is this necessary.
-Dude, it's a really big client, okay?
They are trying to open
ten co-working spaces
in the next two years. Just imagine.
-I got you guys donuts.
-Donuts?
But what about lunch?
-Lunch?
-Yeah.
Dude, will you say something?
I don't mind chicken club sandwich
with peach iced tea.
Yeah. Kavya, what is your budget?
Okay.
-Hero, come here.
-Yes.
-You didn't know?
-No.
I thought bonsai was a plant
like other plants.
Bonsai can be made out of the seeds
of real trees.
-Any tree?
-Any tree.
Okay.
Bonsai literally means
"to plant in a container."
And it's meant to focus on inner harmony.
Do you understand?
And it helps to grow.
Exercise the idea of effort.
And that you forget.
One second, sir.
-This phone will destroy you.
-Yes, Mom.
You didn't get it? Why?
No, I sent it last night.
Yes, I sent it via IMPS.
Did you check it on the app
or on the website?
No, don't go to the bank.
I'll go home and check again.
Yes, I'll do it.
Who did you take the loan from?
So it's okay, it's uncle. It's family.
We can pay later.
Why does it have to be right away?
It's not like we'll run away.
Okay, Mom, I'll go home and do it.
Yes, I'll send that as well.
And check the old one, too.
No, don't say sorry. Stay chill.
Relax. We'll do something.
We'll make it happen. Don't worry.
From Aakash? I don't know.
He's getting married.
Okay, I'll ask him.
All right.
Yes, everything is good. All right.
What did I have for lunch?
I had a tuna sandwich.
Tuna, Mom.
Tuna, Mom, tuna! I'm not shouting.
You couldn't hear me.
Yes. Sorry.
Do you want to learn?
I mean, do you want
to make your own bonsai?
I want to.
Roughly, it will cost 3,000.
I'll get all the raw materials:
soil and magic dust.
Do you want it right away?
No, whenever... I'm going to the nursery
tomorrow, so I thought...
Okay. But don't do it now.
We'll do it later.
All right.
-You let me know.
-Yes.
How's the hibiscus?
It's all right.
Why do I feel like I've seen this before?
-Because you have.
-As in?
We created this presentation before,
we just replaced the images.
-Long live copy and paste.
-Guys, you can't do that.
But there is no time, Kavya.
Of course there is time, dude.
-The client doesn't even care, dude.
-Obviously they do care.
And irrespective of that,
it's our responsibility to--
Kavya, there is no time to do this.
Guys, it's 2:00 right now, okay?
You have four more hours.
This will take you ten minutes to redo.
You have to redo this.
Guys, finish it.
Dude, am I saying something wrong?
No, you are just being too ambitious.
And that's a bad thing?
It's not. People are used to
taking short-cuts.
When someone doesn't let them do that,
they just start hating that person.
But...
I bet they made a group on Whatsapp
and must be bitching.
Shall I check?
-Is all this normal?
-Yes, dude, it's totally normal.
-And they never caught you?
-Are you crazy?
-Remember where the last Dhanno came from?
-What?
-Money for the Enfield came from there?
-Of course.
-That's great.
-You tell me. How's your job going?
The job is fine.
The students are very intelligent.
I'm the one who freaks out.
Dude, Aakash, tell me something--
Listen to me. Never get married.
Yes. What? Why? What happened?
Everything is so expensive.
And you are already broke.
Tell me,
you are coming for the wedding, right?
Yes, I'm coming.
-And you're bringing Kavya, right?
-Yes, she'll come as well.
Okay. That's great. See you.
-Okay then.
-Okay, bye.
DHRUV: AT LEAST, SAY GOOD LUCK
SUPER NERVOUS
What the fuck!
It's not that big a deal, man.
Of course, it's a big deal!
How could you send the wrong pricing
to Yohan? You should have checked!
It's just the price of one bulb.
Yes, but that one bulb is going to be
used in 20 different places, Rohan!
The difference is going to be significant
and you know that.
It's not the final presentation. We are
still working. Will be done by tomorrow.
Not tomorrow. Today.
We are not leaving until this is fixed.
When did you get home?
Tired?
You look tired. Like a tired monkey.
I look ugly as fuck.
Like a tired ugly ass fuck monkey.
Long day?
Long, tiring, frustrating.
-Shall I warm up the pasta?
-I ate it.
-You ate it cold again?
-I was tired.
You should have woken me up, dude.
You were sleeping so nicely.
So what?
-I missed you.
-I missed you, too.
Let's go to sleep, Dhruv.
I have to reach early tomorrow.
What time is it?
What? It's 1:45.
You returned so late. What were you
doing in the office? Did you eat there?
-Sister, where is Kavya?
-She must be in the other room.
Give me something.
You're crazy. Go now.
-What was that?
-Joke.
How come you were listening
to one of his jokes?
Because he was upset.
About what?
Sorry. Don't tell mother.
-Sister? Take the almonds.
-Yes?
I already had some, Lata.
Those are for Dhruv.
Why does brother...
What were you doing?
I need money.
You need money?
-Don't forget to take your lunch box.
-Okay.
-And bring back the other one.
-Yes, for sure. Promise.
Why do you need money?
Mobile.
You want a mobile?
-Why?
-To play.
How much money will you get like this?
I won't tell your mom.
But will you listen to me?
You can get a phone like this,
but it won't be your phone.
Right?
Work hard. Study a lot.
Get good grades.
Then Sister Lata and I
will gift you a phone ourselves.
Then you'll be able to enjoy it.
You'll be able to play a lot,
because it will be your phone.
All right?
Stealing things doesn't make them ours.
Hard work makes them ours.
Will you remember this?
And don't do this again, all right?
For a week now, I've been noticing
that money goes missing from my wallet.
First, I thought it was you.
But then I thought and,
you know, maybe I wasn't careful
with my calculations or something.
Today I saw him.
-Poor thing.
-Shit, man.
Dhruv, it's so sad.
He was so scared when I saw him.
So, I asked him to tell me a joke.
He was saying something.
He looked so cute.
He was crying and telling me.
The elephant lost his shorts,
so he went to the river bank
to find the, ant and then I don't know
what happened. But some bell rang.
Anyway, you ask him.
And, listen, be normal with him, okay?
Aren't you late?
I am. But I informed them.
This was important, right?
-Okay, I'll leave.
-You kept the nutribar?
-I did. Get the shower fixed, okay?
-Yes, for sure.
Okay, bye.
Thanks.
Okay.
It's game night at Sushmita's.
You want to go tonight?
Yes, we'll see.
We'll go, if we feel like it.
Or we can just stay at home
and watch a film.
Cool. We'll figure it out. Bye.
Yeah. Bye.
EXIT "WE SHALL OVERCOME" GROUP?
Subtitle Translation by: Neeti Ray