-You brushed your teeth, right?
-What? Shut up, dude.
Oh, Lata, it's you!
Oh, Lata, it is you!
-Is Mom here?
-She will be here soon.
-What's in the bag?
-Chili pepper salsa.
What did I eat?
-Flatbread and vegetables?
-Yes.
-Yes! And what did I eat?
-Eggs!
-Good one.
-May I tell your mom a joke?
Not my mom, but hers--
No, no!
No, Sonu. I'll listen to your jokes today.
But just don't tell any joke to my mother!
Idiot! Tell me! I wanna hear it.
Dhruv?
-What's up?
-What are you doing? It's been 20 minutes.
Yeah, I know. I'll be right out.
Here, Mom got this for you.
Wow. But we can get this downstairs.
Never mind.
-See? That's my mom.
-Wow. Show me.
Dude, so nice.
-Wow, so pretty.
-This is me.
Dude, that's so cute.
I asked her to get some old photos.
You also ask your mom.
Yes.
-You look nice today.
-What?
-I look like this every day.
-Really?
Go, sit with her.
Yes, I'll come in a minute.
What's wrong? Does it feel awkward?
Yes, it does feel a bit awkward.
I'm freaking out, I don't know why.
-But you've met her before.
-I know.
-I don't feel awkward with your parents.
-What a thing to say.
It's a bit more real each time.
I understand. It's okay.
What are you doing?
Anyway, I'll be fine in five minutes.
What's the plan?
The plan is...
I got a call and I have to go to work.
It's important.
-Fuck you, Kulkarni.
-Momo, listen!
Don't "Momo" me.
It's only a few hours.
You get her to the office after that.
And what about your mom?
What will she think?
She will be upset if I miss work.
Thanks for doing this.
What shit!
My neighbor's son is always on a shoot.
-Really?
-Poor kid. You wouldn't think he's a kid.
Today's parents are eager
for their children to grow up quickly.
-The headache ends.
-It's all due to television.
Making little children work.
-Mom?
-Yes?
Coming.
-At least eat your breakfast.
-I'm done.
Listen, go to the Gateway of India first.
-We went there the last time.
-Yeah.
Right. Go to Banganaga,
then eat at Pizza By The Bay.
If you want Parsi food, go to Britannia.
Jimmy Boy is also great!
You know what?
Dhruv will take care of lunch.
Wow. Thanks for including me in the plan.
Shut up! Then go to Haji Ali and then--
-Siddhivinayak.
-Exactly. Perfect.
Your gooseberry juice is in the fridge.
-Thank you. Now, go.
-I'm going. Don't send me away like that.
Go via the Sea Link.
The cab has been hired for the whole day.
-You have the number?
-Yes. I have everything.
-Perfect. Bye, you guys.
-Bye, honey.
-You want to eat?
-I've already eaten.
Let me know when you want to go out.
Okay, take a shower,
and I will get ready as well.
I already showered.
-You showered?
-Yes, in the morning.
Since I was in the kitchen,
I didn't notice.
Shall I tell you a joke?
Sure, go ahead.
-Shit, I forgot.
-Oh, yeah?
Are you on your way to Siddhivinayak?
Aunty doesn't want to go there.
-Then where are you guys going?
-You won't believe it.
Do you like Shahrukh?
-Yes, you could say that.
-He's my favorite.
-I'll tell you what.
-Yes?
-I'll go closer and look.
-Sure, go on.
-Maybe I'll see him.
-Maybe you will.
-Listen, take a picture.
-Sure.
In front of Mannat. Okay?
Look. It's a bit silly, right?
No, not at all.
Actually, my mom got a picture
just like that, too. Exactly the same.
-Really?
-Yes. When she visited.
Sir, let's go towards Marine Drive.
Since we are in the neighborhood,
shall we see Aamir's home as well?
Sure. Sir, do you know
where Aamir's home is?
-This wasn't fun.
-Why not?
He's such a huge star,
he's done such big movies.
Lagaan, 3 Idiots, PK.
And he lives in an apartment.
You are right.
Shall we go to Marine Drive? Or we
will get late and get stuck in traffic.
-One last thing. Please.
-Why are you saying please?
We'll go where ever you like, okay?
Glamour building is in Bandra, right?
-Glamour?
-Yes.
Who lives in Glamour?
You haven't changed at all.
You look the same.
So do you! I wish you had called.
How come you're here?
Dhruv is showing me around.
My daughter's friend.
Why is he standing there? Come here.
-She is well? How old is she?
-She is 27 and a half.
-She's well, happy.
-You would know better.
Quiet.
-You're meeting after a long time?
-Yes.
-It's been 18 years.
-Eighteen years?
-Yes.
She was never in town
when I came to Mumbai.
-I know.
-This time,
I thought let me try
and see if I can meet her.
I'm very glad.
But next time, stay at my place.
-Yes.
-Yes, we'll have fun.
We'll ask Aparna to join us.
She'll come from Pune.
Yes, the whole gang will be together.
It will be great.
Gang, yes.
-We had a lot of fun together.
-Yes.
The first time we bunked school,
first film, first cigarette,
first beer, first kiss.
Sorry.
How about some tea or coffee?
No, some other time.
-We're running late.
-Sure?
You're going to Juhu, right?
Go to a store called Ashok, number 34.
Make sure you have pav bhaji there.
My goodness, you still remember
that I love pav bhaji?
Of course!
Open the message. A, B, C.
Click on A. And then...
there it is. That's how.
-Wow.
-Simple.
One minute. I'll send you a hello.
Okay.
-See? I got it. Hello.
-Wow.
This is so easy.
Where did you eat pav bhaji from?
-Pav bhaji. From an auto rickshaw.
-From an auto rickshaw?
You were bound to have an upset stomach
if you had pav bhaji at 4 in the morning
from an auto rickshaw.
What happened was that the municipality
got rid of all the food stands.
And Aakash and I were starving.
-Aakash. You both went to his wedding?
-Yes, Kavya and I attended it.
So, anyway, we were hungry
and we saw an auto rickshaw guy
just outside the hostel.
We went to see what he was doing.
He was making pav bhajis
on a stove in the auto rickshaw.
And we were so hungry
we asked him to make some for us.
We took the pav bhaji to our room.
My stomach went crazy
two hours after eating it.
So now even hearing about it
gives me a bad taste in my mouth.
After that day,
I never ate that again.
-I can't.
-Now I get it.
When you said you don't eat pav bhaji,
I thought to myself that there is nothing
that Dhruv does not eat.
I mean, it's a compliment.
You're a foodie, right?
Do your parents know that
the two of you live together?
Yes, Aunty. They know everything.
You're serious about each other, right?
-Yes, full power. Don't worry about it.
-Full power?
I mean,
we're quite serious about each other.
Okay.
-Kavya is all right, isn't it?
-Yes, she is.
-She's just busy.
-Yes.
She's very happy with her new job
and very busy as well.
-Does that trouble you?
-No.
You know, the first time
we got Kavya to the beach,
she couldn't understand where
all the water came from.
-So cute.
-And she kept asking,
"Where does the water end?
Why can't we see anything beyond it?
-What is beyond it?"
-So cute.
She was so excited.
And very confused, too.
If it was happening now,
take out your phone and record.
Yes, but I don't know.
Maybe if we had recorded it,
I wouldn't have remembered it.
I'm sorry about what Anu said.
No, Aunty. Why the apology?
-It was awkward for you.
-No, not at all.
Please, don't think that.
I have a request.
Sure. Tell me.
Please, don't tell Kavya what Anu said.
I mean, it's not right.
I'm her mother, so...
No. I won't tell her. Don't worry.
-I'm trusting you.
-Yes.
-You promise?
-I promise.
Thank you.
Mom, come and eat with us.
-Yes, Aunty, please, come.
-Please, come, Aunty.
Son-in-law, go help her.
Come on. Get up. Quickly.
I should go and help her.
-Sit down, idiot.
-What's the matter?
You forgot to wash your hands?
No, I did.
-Put the phone away.
-Just one--
-Put it away.
-One for Insta.
-Do it later. Put the phone away.
-Okay.
-I love the lentils.
-Seriously.
Is it just me, or does it need
a little more salt?
-The salt is just right. I love it.
-It's perfect.
It's my mom's specialty.
The lentils need more salt. Add this.
Thank you, Aunty, thank you.
Needs more salt.
Guy, what are you doing?
-What happened?
-Nothing, Mom. Just come.
You have no more flatbread.
Mine? No, I'm fine.
-Take it, honey.
-No, please.
-One more won't hurt.
-Carbs, Ma.
-Carbs.
-Yes, you can leave.
Kavya, think of Dhruv.
He can't even make tea.
Aunty, she's kidding.
I know how to make tea.
You've had it and it was great, right?
I made it with cardamom.
I know he makes great tea.
-Go on, tell us. Why are you nervous?
-I am nervous?
-Go on.
-Who is nervous?
How are things on Tinder? Tell us.
Why are you nervous? Tell us.
Having fun?
What is Tinder?
It brings people together
for work meetings.
For work meetings. It sorts everything.
Mom, that's all you're going to have?
-Carbs.
-Funny. Good one.
-Why are you flattering her?
-Listen, tell me something.
Why doesn't Aamir Khan live in a bungalow?
He must be living in one.
He must have shifted
after his second marriage.
No, he's always lived in an apartment.
-No.
-Yes!
-How does she know all this?
-I know this.
-What's that road? Pali Wali?
-Pali Hill.
Bandra. We went there.
I didn't see any hill.
They call the steep road a hill.
He's making things up.
I'll have some lentils.
-Take from this.
-What?
-What are you doing?
-I got excited and took too much.
-Eat it.
-I did.
-That was for the photo.
-I ate it.
-Yeah.
-Tell me, shall I take more?
-Kavya, you didn't eat anything.
-No, Mom, I am very full.
I'm done.
Aunty, your cab will be here
in two minutes.
You're not going out
of your way for me, right?
-Don't worry, Mom.
-It's on the way.
-Bye, honey.
-Bye.
-Bye, son.
-Bye, Aunty.
-Bye.
Listen, there are cashews and almonds
in the kitchen. On the top shelf.
-Have them.
-Shit! Just a minute.
What happened? What's the matter with her?
-I don't know. The cab is here, right?
-Yes.
-This.
-What is this?
Lata's chili pepper salsa
and gooseberry juice.
-You wanted them.
-Thank you.
I hope she likes the sari.
What did Sonu say the last time?
Sonu said,
"My mom gave that sari to her mom."
My sweet child.
-Let me walk you out.
-No, honey.
-We'll take her.
-You are tired.
-Okay.
-Bye, guys. Good night.
-Thanks.
-Okay.
-Bye, Aunty.
-Bye.
-Love you, honey.
-Love you, too.
-Hey, Tinku. Come here.
-I don't feel like it.
What difference does it make?
Where do memes come from?
Who invented them?
But they help to pass the time
and entertain.
You okay?
-How are you feeling?
-Good. Great. Amazing.
Listen, did Aunty say anything about me?
What? Nothing?
When could she have said anything?
You were with her all the time.
-I'll ask her in a few days.
-Yes, ask.
-Did she say anything about me?
-Yes, just general stuff.
How is she? How is she doing?
How is her work?
She is busy these days, right?
Yes, she is busy with her work.
I miss her already.
You will see her soon.
You shouldn't have brought up that
Tinder thing with Akshara.
She's trying to get over that guy.
You should have let her be.
-Dude, it was just a small joke.
-I know.
Anyway, she started it.
Do you want some green tea?
Or do you want your chamo... whatever?
-I'll have my chamomile.
-Cool.
Dhruv, you know, sometimes I think...
the way our parents got married
is so nice, right?
As in? Love marriage or arranged marriage?
No, I'm not talking in terms of
love marriage or arranged marriage.
Just think about it.
Whatever they share is so nice.
They've spend all their lives
just with each other.
Every experience that they've shared,
it's only been with that one person.
That's so nice.
I mean, they've not even kissed
anyone else but each other.
Isn't that nice?
Yeah, it's actually very nice.
What?
No, what?
What, what, why?
I know that face, Dhruv.
I know what it means.
What face? What are you talking about?
-You want green tea?
-Tell me.
-What are you doing? Tell you what?
-Say it.
-Say what?
-Dhruv.
Kavya.
You know...
I will feel really bad about myself.
I feel like that already. Inside.
Please. Please, let this go.
Fine. Swear on my life.
Swear on my life and promise
that you will not tell Aunty.
What are you doing?
You haven't crossed your toes, right?
Dhruv, shut up!
This is important for the future.
I'm telling the truth. I'm not kidding.
What happened?
-Dude, you can't tell her.
-I won't.
-You swore.
-Dhruv, this is not about you.
What did she say about her first kiss?
She just said first kiss. I don't know.
Yes, but was it Mom
or was it someone else?
Obviously, this was something
I wasn't going to ask about.
What are you thinking?
Why wouldn't she tell me this?
Because mothers won't tell their kids
about first kiss.
Why not? And it's not
just about this kiss, okay?
She has this childhood friend
living here for I don't know how long,
and I don't even know who she is!
Who is this woman?
She kept saying she keeps traveling,
haven't met for a while--
This is too frustrating.
Why can't she share this with me?
What did she say afterwards?
Nothing. Don't tell Kavya
because I'm her mother,
-it won't be nice if she comes to know.
-Nice!
Why does she have to be nice?
Why does everything have to be nice?
Why is that important?
Why can't she be herself for once with me
and not be nice?
You know, even when Grandpa feel ill
she didn't tell me.
-Am I a child?
-You are a child.
I mean, you are a child. Her child.
You're not really a child.
You are a working woman.
Do you know I have a feeling that I will
never really know who this person is!
She's so busy being my mother,
she's so busy being nice
that I'm never going to know her!
Isn't that sad?
-Will this happen to us, too?
-No.
Why will we make the same mistake?
But it's such a depressing thought.
-Are you getting what I'm trying to say?
-Yeah.
I understand.
There will be things about my mother
that I will not know because--
Yeah, because they are going to
remain mothers.
They are never going to be themselves
with us.
I think I should talk to her.
No, you're not talking to her. You--
Not about this, Dhruv!
I'll have a normal conversation with her.
What do you mean by normal?
You talk to her every day, right?
Yes, I do that.
I think I should talk to her
about our sex life.
What? Are you crazy? What are you saying?
No, please, okay?
I have to do something.
Shit! Your chamomile tea!
-What happened? Whose message was it?
-Mom's.
-Did she say anything about me?
-Dhruv!
What?
Why are you getting annoyed?
I'm just asking. It's a normal question.
She just said she's reached the station
and she's left some money.
What can we do?
Now my mom is calling.
Listen, it's very simple.
Just go on a holiday with her
for a few days,
spend time with her. Maybe that's the
thing! You haven't spent time with her.
Maybe it's about that. Okay?
Just give me a second.
Hi, Nadi.
Subtitle Translation by