My God.
Are you okay?
Shit. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to wake you up.
-No, it's fine.
-Must be some allergy.
Come here. Good morning.
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
You gave me a bath for no reason.
You know I don't shower on Sundays.
-Gross.
-Sorry.
It was a sneeze. It happens.
Come here.
Kavu? You have fever.
I don't feel so good.
-So lie down, it's Sunday. Take rest.
-I'll sweat it out.
What? Sweat it out?
Why are you being so hardcore?
Come and lie down.
-I have plans.
-What plans?
I have to go for a run,
then I have to go to
the smoothie-making workshop.
Then I have to go to the parlor.
And then I have to go to the flea market.
I'll make the smoothie.
-Why do you have to go to the parlor?
-Manicure, pedicure.
Wait.
Here you go. Book it.
-I'm sick.
-So?
You can still try and feel good
when you're sick. Book it. My treat.
Experience everything.
Doesn't it sound like a Dubai tourism ad?
Shall I sell the idea?
I'll make a lot of money.
This is so fuck-all, dude.
I get just one Sunday
and I had to get sick.
It's okay. You lie down. Get some rest.
-Take a Crocin and you will be fine.
-Are you my mother?
Crocin for everything.
Take a Crocin for this.
Take a Crocin for that.
-Whatever happens, take a Crocin.
-What else should I give you?
You have fever. You'll be fine.
Just take a Crocin.
I'm just irritated. You come fast.
-What is it?
-Moonlight.
-Really, Dhruv?
-Yes, really.
You are the one who wants so many things.
I just want one thing.
My mutton cutlet gravy.
I don't even get that.
I keep chanting Moonlight, Moonlight,
Moonlight like a fool.
-Fuck you, man.
-No, fuck you, dude.
Your face is a fuck-you.
Lie down comfortably.
Apart from manicure and pedicure,
what other services do you offer?
Ma'am, we offer facials, hair,
all salon services.
Wow. See?
This is luxury. A luxurious  life.
Seriously, Kulkarni.
-See!
-Very pretty.
-Ma'am, sure you won't have anything?
-No, sir, thank you.
-Just let me know.
-Yes, sir, thank you.
Here. Bon appetite.
-It looks very beautiful.
-Doesn't it?
-This flower.
-That's what I meant.
Hibiscus. It bloomed today.
I thought since your food wasn't
looking good, I'd make it look good.
How can you eat that?
With my mouth.
Why are you frowning?
It's Sunday. Cheat day. Let's enjoy it.
What are the rest of the days
for you, Dhruv?
I love you, dude.
Fuck you.
I wasn't talking to you.
I was talking to the sandwich.
Why you being mean to me?
Ma'am, this is done.
Would you like anything else done?
It's your treat, right, Dhruv?
What else should I get done?
Well played.
-Here, take a bit. Trophy. Hello?
-Thanks.
It doesn't make a difference.
Don't do that.
Don't do that, dude! Why are you
doing that? Annoying me needlessly.
It's fun.
Shall we watch Silver Linings?
No, I've watched it many times.
Won't watch it again.
So what's on the list?
You're checking a girl out?
-No. I mean yes.
-How shameless.
-She's just a girl.
-I've seen it. No need to hide
She was in my course in college, okay?
-In your course?
-Yes.
I thought your math course
didn't have pretty girls.
She left to somewhere else
after two weeks.
So I was checking to see where she went.
-Where did she go?
-So much concern.
She must have gotten confused between
psychology and math. Poor thing.
She popped up in suggested friends.
Genuinely came up in suggested friends.
It's Facebook's fault, not mine.
Mark is a bastard.
You couldn't say that before?
Okay, well. Mark is a bastard.
No, dude! Why do you keep sneezing
in my face?
Why not there?
Want to make me sick?
Shut up and look at the list.
-Let's watch films.
-Now you wait and watch. 90s special.
-Coolie No.1. Hero No.1.
-Dude. No.
-Dulhe Raja. What?
-Dhruv?
I'm not in the mood for these films.
Yeah, but there were actually good films.
Now everyone pretends to be cool.
Tell me.
Terminator 1?
-God bless you. Terminator 2?
-Sorry.
-Don't want to watch that.
-Terminator 3?
Dhruv, be creative, dude.
What do you mean by that?
I don't remember what happened.
-What happened?
-It doesn't matter.
I want to watch a different film.
-Monsters Inc.?
-Dhruv, you know what?
I'm really tired, okay?
We've spent more time in deciding what to
watch instead of actually watching it.
-Jajantaram Mamantara.
-Dhruv!
Okay. Wait. So what do you want to do?
-Start/Stop?
-Okay, go!
Okay. Start!
-Stop!
-"K."
"K." All right, come on, "K."
-"K, k, k..."
The first film is Kama Sutra, Dhruv.
Should we see it?
-Actually, I've seen it, dude.
-Really?
-Yeah, I mean, I've seen all the scenes.
-Obviously.
We used to skip tuition,
go to the cybercafe and do this.
What an education, man. Sex education.
-Let's watch it.
-Yes!
Today I'll find out what the story was.
Actually, you know what? You watch it.
-I'll just finish some work.
-Turn that way.
There will be no more sneezes.
Night cycling in Bombay
sounds like a nice plan, no?
Can you please get excited
about at least one plan?
Yes, dude, it sounds all right.
Cycle on.
This stew is really nice. Thank you.
Thank you.
Every time I fall sick,
I feel like eating khichdi.
Mom has made it a habit.
You know the worst part
about falling sick?
Nothing tastes good.
But I hope I feel better by tomorrow.
If someone coughs in the office,
even accidentally,
everyone stares at that person
like they're a criminal.
Dhruv, I'm talking to you, no?
Tell me something.
Why does pizza
always taste better the next day?
-Because you enjoy it more.
-Yes. But why?
Only two or three slices are left.
You fully enjoy it.
No, but mutton also tastes better.
Beans also taste better the next day.
It's not that, it's something else.
There is something.
Shit, dude, I should have
photographed the stew.
Should have put that on Instagram.
My followers aren't increasing.
What do I do?
-Put my photo.
-No. Cheap tactics.
I prefer my food over your face.
On Instagram, silly. Not in life.
Are you mad? No, no, no!
Infection.
Green tea. Dude, you need green tea.
You were coughing just now, right?
I'll get you green tea. Green tea. Yes!
At least you said something, you asshole.
It's evening.
The sound of the evening prayer on
a Sunday evening is depressing, no?
Why?
Because it reminds you
that the weekend is over.
But you love working.
But I love this more.
I love the evening prayer.
When I was a kid,
I used to come home from school,
I used to watch Dexter or Scooby Doo.
Then Vandana didi used to put me to sleep.
And when I heard the evening prayer,
I would wake up.
And then, exactly 15 minutes later,
Mom would come home from work.
So this sound reminds me of
my mom coming home. Always.
Have you fallen asleep?
No, dude.
It's so nice, no, how different people
relate to the same things differently?
Dhruv, I'm feeling better now.
I think I should take a shower.
-First get it fixed!
-I'll get it fixed tomorrow.
Fine. Then I will bathe tomorrow.
You are such a bad influence.
Don't tell your mother that.
How was it?
-What?
-The tea. Did you taste any difference?
-What did you do?
-I added fennel.
You didn't notice any difference?
I can't taste anything.
Good. I didn't give you my pizza.
It would have been pointless.
-See.
-What is this?
Mom is cleaning the cuboards.
So she found all this old stuff.
These are my drawings
from third grade.
Okay. But what is this?
This was my summer vacation project
that year.
The teacher had asked us to draw
the places that we wanted to visit.
And that year,
we were going to take a Euro trip.
The usual nine nights, ten days.
But then the company's manager quit,
and then Dad had to step in
so we didn't go.
What?
That sucks, man.
I know I was really sad,
and I didn't even know
what to do for this project.
So I drew these.
I really wanted to go to all these places.
You drew all this in the third grade?
-You must be good at geography.
-Much better than you.
-Why is everything a competition?
-It is.
-Come on then.
-Let's do it.
-You just like to lose.
-Sit straight.
-Ready?
-Yes. Begin.
-Name a country with "Z."
-Zimbabwe.
Name a city with "Q."
-Quito, the capital of Ecuador.
-Yes, of course.
-You didn't know that.
-I knew that. Shut up.
Name a mountain, river or lake
that starts with "K."
-Kilimanjaro. That was easy.
-Shit.
Name a city with "X."
With "X."
-Hurry up, you can't take so much time.
-Yes, one second.
Tick, tick, one. Tick, tick, two.
Xiaomi!
I asked for a city name,
not a phone company.
It is based there. Xiaomi is from Xiaomi.
I'm telling the truth. I am not lying.
You tell me.
Xianning.
-Yes, Xianning!
-Yes, it is!
In China. Right next to Beijing.
-Look it up.
-Yes.
Xianning.
-I want to go to all these places.
-Where? Xianning and Xiaomi?
-Don't joke, I'm serious.
-It's not possible.
Why would you say that?
-It's such a horrible thing to say.
-Easy.
It's actually not possible, no?
How is it possible?
Just like I know that in this lifetime,
I can't buy a home at Marine Drive.
I can't become a professional footballer.
Why weep over what is not possible?
Enjoy what you have. Simple.
-I can't look at it that way.
-Why not? What's wrong with that?
I think if you dream about something,
and you work towards it,
you can achieve it.
It's not the way you think.
This is all from the The Alchemist.
It has messed up your mind.
But anyway, what works for you,
works for you.
What works for me, works for me.
You are crazy.
What is this, dude?
-What?
-This.
Why did you keep that on this?
-I'm sorry, I didn't realize it.
-Didn't realize it?
I didn't do it on purpose, Dhruv.
You could have kept it alive for one day.
Will you relax? It's a flower.
Let it be. You won't get it.
-You need to chill.
-I need to chill?
What is this, dude?
Okay, I'll be careful next time.
Anyway, you should work a bit.
Why are you so bothered suddenly?
No, you should work.
It will reduce your workload.
-Really?
-Yeah, work a little.
I thought you hate it
when I work on weekends.
No.
-Okay, work for 90 minutes.
-What is going on?
-Liverpool has a game.
-The match is about to start?
-Yes, yes.
-So just say that.
-Why are you playing games, Komolika?
-What? Komolika?
Where did she come from?
Fuck, what is she doing now?
-Komolika. Anyway, ta-ta, bye-bye.
-No, no!
You can watch it
but can you please watch it here?
No. Big screen, small screen.
Don't ruin it.
-Please? Please.
-No, dude.
-Fine.
-Okay.
Listen, you should draw more, you know.
I know.
You should doodle. You don't do anything.
I miss it, too. I will.
But not today. I'm sick, no?
Sloth bear is back.
Fuck! Fuck!
It was a last second goal, dude.
Last minute goal. Fuck!
What the fuck are you doing?
You were sleeping and I couldn't shout.
Sorry, but, I really wanted to scream
and I really wanted to say fuck you
to everyone.
Even to you. Fuck!
Who scored?
Was it a one-range goal by Salah
or Mané took a solo goal?
I go crazy
when you ask questions like that,
it makes me so happy.
Take all my money, dude.
You have money to give?
Shut up and understand feelings.
And it's not "Mai-ne" it's Mané.
Mané. Fuck! What a tap in by Firmino!
Last second, dude, last second.
It doesn't happen so quickly.
-Anything else?
-How crazy, dude!
Fuck!
I'll go get some water.
Crazy.
Why so many mosquitoes?
Is the All Out switched on?
You didn't put post the khichdi photos
on Instagram.
Actually I made two.
One for you and one for me.
Yours was bland and mine was spicy.
I don't know which one to post.
Are you crazy? Why are you laughing?
-Karma.
-Karma?
I don't want to get ill.
What does karma have to do with it?
Come, let me see.
-It's nothing.
-It's nothing, dude.
-It must be an allergy.
-Allergy to what?
Everything is the same.
We've been in the same room all day.
I don't know about you,
I'm feeling better now.
Yeah? Very good.
Listen, don't feel bad.
-What's up?
-I'm just being honest.
-You'r stinking.
-What?
I'm stinking?
I stink?
Kavya, do you know that
for the past few hours
it's you who has been stinking?
You nose just cleared.
Smell yourself. Smell.
Like it?
Why didn't you tell me about it before?
I've been through far worse.
This is nothing.
-Stop talking about yourself.
-Buzz off.
Sleep here, there's place.
This is my spot. You threw me there
this afternoon, too.
I feel sleepy here,
this is where I will sleep. Move.
-Move, move.
-Stop being mean.
I hope the mosquitoes don't bite, dude.
Good nuts.
Good night.