Kavya, what are you doing?
Just finishing some work, Dhruv.
Go to sleep.
You sleep as well.
We have to be up in a few hours.
Kavya?
Sleep, no?
Just give me two minutes, Dhruv.
-Come, Dhruv, we're late.
-Dude.
-Thank you, Madam.
-You're welcome.
Shall we take the bags?
How is it that your bag
is heavier than mine?
-How is it heavier? It's the same.
-Exactly.
-Are you wearing a lehenga as well?
-No.
I couldn't decide which suit to wear,
so I'm taking both both.
Two suits, two shirts, two pants,
two ties, two shoes. Two of everything.
For two days? You are ridiculous.
Yes. Did you take medicine?
Wow. Damn nice room, dude?
-Yeah.
-Aakash has made it in life.
He's having fun.
What is the Wi-Fi password?
Guess what? Tub bath, bitches!
-Bathtub, Dhruv.
-That's what I meant.
Fuck, did you get hurt?
Sorry, I was aiming for that corner.
You're okay? Now move away
or the next one will hit you.
Dhruv, how do I connect to the Wi-Fi?
-Forget about work. Okay, show me--
-No, wait, I'm figuring it out.
Fuck, dude.
This is how weddings should be.
A holiday along with the wedding.
Fun for the guests, right?
-Hotels beds are so comfy, right? So soft.
-I swear.
And it smells so good here.
Yep. Wait. What did you say?
Soft and comfy!
And creepy.
-What is this?
-Show me.
"Welcome to Nandini and Aakash's wedding.
We're super excited
to have you present at our wedding.
It's going to be nuts.
Below is the schedule.
Please make sure you're there on time.
Music and Henna at 12 a.m.
Pool party 3 p.m.
-Cocktail party 8 p.m."
-What time is it now?
-It's 11:53.
-Dude, what the fuck?
-But when was the wedding?
-That's tomorrow in the court.
We have just seven minutes to chill.
I know.
Why are weddings so hectic?
Why aren't they chill?
They should be chill, right?
Like a holiday.
-Anyway, I'm going to go to the loo.
-No, I'm going. Shotgun!
-What? I said it first.
-Yeah. But I said shotgun first.
-Who says that anymore?
-I said it.
-It's not valid.
-Yes, it's always valid.
Dhruv, help me with the Wi-Fi, dude.
I'm in the loo, dude.
Please!
Some kids just have a mature face, no?
As if they have come in this world
to hate on everyone.
-Who are you talking about?
-That kid over there.
Fuck, what happened to him?
Why is he so serious?
I think he is thinking
about his father's inheritance.
Yeah. No. He's thinking about...
Maybe he is thinking of coming out
in front of his parents.
No, no. Maybe he is thinking of
his dead sibling.
What? Are you crazy?
Why are you saying such things?
It's a wedding. Look at that.
Maybe he is thinking
when will Dhruv and Kavya get married.
Interesting.
Maybe he is thinking Dhruv and Kavya
are fine they are now.
Son, where is Mom? She's still not here.
Mom is still in the loo.
Dad, I controlled myself.
I pushed it back inside.
Wow, my son is so smart. Come along.
-Pushed it back inside.
-Potty it was.
Potty it was.
-I feel like I have to poop.
-Stop it, dude.
Is that why you look so constipated?
I've been smiling at everyone
since this morning.
My mouth is stuck like this.
-The setup is really nice.
-Isn't it?
-It's been done by the Wedding Brigade.
-Nice, dude, very nice.
They were right here.
I'll send you the link.
You guys can check it out too.
Guys, shall we get our picture taken?
The line is getting longer.
-Yes.
-Yes. Come on, let's smile.
You don't have to smile for this picture.
Yes, actually, let's not.
At least the photo will be realistic.
Okay.
This is very annoying.
The black one was all right.
Just one more day, Dhruv.
-Take this.
-Thanks.
Shit, I forgot to get the green chutney.
-Should I get it?
-No, it's okay.
It's very crowded.
Look at the line over there.
That could mean anything.
You could be talking about food.
About anything.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Look at this.
-Dude, this is fucked up!
-It looks scary.
-Was she a bat?
That's what! So I was on top of her,
and she was like,
"Choke me, choke me!"
It was like being part of
a porn film, dude.
I'm so glad that something exciting
happened in my life.
Otherwise, it's the same old thing.
This is spicy.
I agree with you.
-When I was with Ray--
-Who is Ray?
That 48-years-old ancient dude.
-The one with eight girlfriends.
-Yes, that one.
Did you know she met his kids?
It's okay, dude.
I mean, he was honest with me, right?
It's not like he was lying to me.
He respected me, he treated me well.
And on the surface, it was weird.
But he was always there for me.
-Dude, she must have been into BDSM.
-Who?
Her. The mosquito. The bat woman.
Look at this.
Just think about
what Bombay BDSM must be like.
Under blue plastic sheets.
Plastic sheets sex, bro!
Thank you.
Do you want more?
Do you want the water? Why?
What are you thinking?
Nothing. What are you thinking?
I'm just really tired. I think
I'm going to go upstairs and sleep.
Dhruv, just one second.
I'll just call you back in a minute.
Dhruv, can you please hurry up?
What happened?
-Nothing. Just hurry up.
-Am I hurting you?
No, I just need to finish some work.
Seriously?
What happened?
What the fuck do you mean what happened?
-Why would you say that?
-Say what?
The hurry up! And, you know,
the work thing. Why would you say that?
Because the work thing was on my mind,
and you were not hurrying up.
Hurrying up?
What are you saying?
At least think about what you are saying.
What is the matter?
Why are you overreacting?
Am I overreacting?
Dude, we're trying to have sex here
and this is what you say?
"Dhruv, hurry up,"
and you had this pissed off face.
-I wasn't pissed off.
-You should have seen yourself.
You could have said the same thing
with love, nicely, with respect.
Why say it with irritation?
You really made me feel as if I am...
As if I'm forcing you
to have sex with me, man.
-What the--
-No, I mean it.
It's not a nice feeling.
Don't do that again.
Fine, I'm sorry.
But the work thing was really--
Stop this work thing. Work, work, work!
Don't talk about it!
-I'm sick and tired of this shit.
-Sick of what? Me working?
No! Are you deaf?
Will you stop talking to me like that?
You're making me feel guilty
-for wanting to work hard.
-What?
I'm making you feel guilty?
What is going on, Kavya?
Why are you talking like this?
Work as much as you want to, man.
Really. Work as much as you want to.
I'm there to support you.
Be happy for you.
All I'm saying is
that when we are together,
that when we have our little world,
don't bring anything else in.
Let this be our special place.
Why is the world coming between us, man?
Keep the two apart.
Look at everyone else, dude.
Everyone is having so much fun.
We couldn't even have sex!
Why are you comparing yourself
with others?
I thought you were happy
with what we have.
Maybe I'm not, dude.
Okay. Okay. So so let's talk about it.
-No, fuck, it.
-No, tell me.
When did I not care? When wasn't I there?
No, Dhruv,
you have to talk to me right now!
Okay, you know what? Fuck it.
Dude, I bought a bird-feeder.
I thought we'd install it together.
I texted you. What the fuck did you do?
You just ignored my text.
You could have at least replied.
And when my friend Sandeep
came from Delhi.
He came just once. For one day.
We had to go for dinner.
It was 50 minutes late.
-I was getting vada pav for your friend!
-It doesn't take 50 minutes.
-It didn't take 50 minutes.
-However long it took!
I text you every day like a fool, dude.
Fuck replying. You make me feel as if
you are ignoring me.
Half the time
I'm talking to myself it seems.
During your off-site,
you didn't even message me once.
I'm only begging you,
"What are you doing?"
Do you think I'm crazy?
Every day, I say the same thing,
"Let's go, mutton cutlet gravy."
I keep repeating it like a fool.
But you don't even listen to me.
Just surprise me once.
Come, let's go today.
And that moment,
one fucking moment,
when I was slightly in doubt,
when I was slightly vulnerable,
when I wasn't sure if I did
the right thing regarding my job,
I thought I'd talk to you
and what did you do?
Dude, you scolded me.
You were trying to make me feel bad
and you know it.
Fuck everything, dude.
Even for your own mother--
Sorry, I shouldn't have said that.
But what can I do?
This is on my mind.
Why didn't you say this
when it was happening?
Why did you have to keep it inside of you?
I didn't keep it inside.
Of course you did. Obviously you did!
I saw it and I was like,
it's okay, it happens.
It just went past.
But now I see the pattern.
Now I see. Now I'm joining the dots.
I'm like fuck, man!
You are changing!
You are in your own world.
I am changing? Why?
Because I am working hard every day?
Has it ever occurred to you
why I work so hard today?
That maybe it's because
I care about our future
-and our security unlike you.
-Unlike me?
-I don't care about us?
-No.
I don't?
No, Dhruv.
What the fuck do you mean by that?
Tell me.
Maybe you do, okay? But I think...
I think you're quite careless
and immature or whatever the hell--
How the hell am I immature, man?
What have I done?
I work, dude. I make money.
Not as much as you.
But that doesn't mean anything, right?
-Because I am also trying to work.
-That's not the point.
I know you are working, but you
don't think of the future the way I do.
-Money is important to me!
-I know that.
No! Money is important to me
for us to have a good, secure future!
-I know that!
-No, it really, really matters!
-No, you don't!
I know that.
I know it's important to you.
-No, it's different.
-How is it different?
-It is! You don't get it!
-How?
-It is, Dhruv!
-How is it different?
Do not touch me.
-How is it different? Tell me.
-It's different and you don't get it,
because if you did, then we
wouldn't having discussion.
Man!
We are having this fight right now
because you have this face that told me
that, "Dhruv, I have problem with you
having sex with me now."
What the fuck are you talking about?
Shut up!
Will you stop dramatizing everything?
You're making it sound worse
than what it was.
I just had that work thing on my mind
and I couldn't stop thinking
about it, okay?
I can't let go of things like you do.
I can't joke off things like you do.
-I can't act like--
-What do you mean by that?
No, what? Say it!
Say it!
-Your PhD?
-Fuck, same shit again!
-You quit your job.
-Again?
No, why? Let's talk about it.
You want to talk, I'm talking.
There's nothing to talk about,
it's not complicated.
I... was... getting... bored!
I wasn't enjoying myself.
-So I quit.
-You cannot quit things like that.
-You can't start quitting everything.
-You know what?
Yes, I can.
It's just that
I don't want to be slowed down.
And I don't want to be pulled back, okay?
Am I pulling you back?
Yes, Dhruv.
I'm sorry. Maybe slightly, but you are.
Fuck, man.
Dhruv, you don't care about our future.
You don't care about security.
You don't care about money.
Because you choose not to.
Cause you are just fine with everything.
Everything is okay.
-No, I am not.
-Of course, you are, Dhruv!
You are fine with having a bath
with a bucket and a mug--
What's the problem with a bucket
and a mug?
-What's the big deal?
-Exactly. See? You never get it.
There is nothing wrong with
having a bath with bucket and mug.
But if you can do better than that,
then you should.
I've been asking you
to fix that shower forever.
But you didn't
Cause you are fine.
You have a problem with it, not me.
If you have a problem ,
fix it yourself.
Why should I do everything?
You have to help me out here.
Help you out? Don't I work?
Do I watch TV all day at home?
Do it yourself. And you know what?
The first time I'm going to do
when I get back is get that shit fixed!
I've told you,
the issue is not at our end.
That bastard secretary
doesn't pick up my calls. What do I do?
But I'll get it fixed. You enjoy there.
You take 20 minute shower there.
As if you have the time to do that!
-As if you're enjoying the tub bath--
-Bathtub.
Fine, bathtub, tub bath!
Fuck, you don't like me, man.
No, that's the truth.
You don't like who I am actually.
You don't.
You have a serious problem with who I am.
And, honestly,
if it's that bad, you should find
someone like that fucking roadie.
In your own words,
he loved planning, right?
So just go ahead with it.
Kavya, maybe he is your type,
and I am not.
You're a liar.
No, I'm not.
I meant each and every word
that I said that night.
Listen.
See, I care about this, man!
What we have right now!
This moment! Us! Us in this.
You think I don't care about this?
Do you know how difficult it is to plan it
and then manage to achieve that?
Do you think it's easy to try and be happy
and not chase something?
It's the same thing for me.
-It's not!
-For you!
Can't you see you're letting go
of what we have right now
because you are so worried about tomorrow?
Kavu, look at Keshav. He died, right?
We used to beat him at football.
Suddenly, one day he just died, man!
That's exactly why
we need to be prepared, Dhruv.
You can't not plan for the future
because you are so scared of growing up
and so scared of investing in it.
Let it go for now.
You keep planning and don't enjoy a thing.
-I know what the fuck I'm doing.
-No, you don't. I don't think you do.
Every time I say
let's go to a new restaurant,
every time I say
let's try something new to eat,
have a new experience,
you put a stop to it.
Because you want to go to the same places,
you want to eat the same food,
you want to do the same things,
-again and again and again!
-You know why?
-Because that is us!
-No, Dhruv, this is us!
It can be us, in fact!
It's not, man. It's not.
You don't think so
because you don't give it a chance.
You said you'll stand by me!
You said you'll support me!
You said we're a team
and these are your words.
I'm not making this up.
It's just that you are changing so much.
It's not change, it's growth!
Yes, but it's coming at a cost.
What cost?
I can't...
-Laundry, sir?
-Yes.
Just wait a second.
Don't give your tie.
I've got you a new one, it's in my bag.
Where did you get this Liverpool tie from?
Satellite Mall.
I went there last night.
-Here.
-Thank you, sir.
Subtitle Translation by Neeti Ray