Bro. Nice tie.
Thanks.
Where did you get it?
She got it, dude.
From Satellite Mall in Bombay.
She gifted your a Liverpool tie?
What a girlfriend, bro.
Hey, bro.
Are you eating?
-Why is everyone so dressed up?
-Let it go.
I want to see what bit you.
Sorry! Fuck!
Sorry!
Have a lemon!
Nice. Come on, Kavya!
Come on, make her drink. Yes.
-I will take it.
-Yes. Drink.
Nice. Now it's your turn, buddy.
-No, dude, let it be.
-What do you mean?
-I don't feel like it. Will drink beer.
-It's not Mr. Rao's booze. It's mine.
It's my wedding. Please, tell him.
Drink, you jerk.
Nice!
-What are you doing?
-Wait and see.
You're not happy at the wedding?
Bastards! Assholes!
Fuck! Fuck you guys!
-Fucking assholes, dogs! Fuck, fuck!
-What happened? Aakash?
What is it?
-Why aren't the waiters getting us food?
-Sorry?
Nothing.
I'll just come back.
Look. There is green chutney as well.
It's his first day,
so I wished him luck from our side.
Okay.
Hold this, I'm getting a call.
Aakash is calling.
Yes, what's up?
What? Right now? Is everything all right?
Okay, I'll be there in a minute.
I'll be right back.
This is a romantic moment, right?
Sorry. Everyone is wasted.
I had to disturb you.
Are you crazy?
I'll tell this to your kids.
That I zipped their father's pants
on his wedding day.
-Shut up. The wedding is good, right?
-Yes, it's great.
I love the beds! They are so... jumpy!
Have you...
-What?
-Had sex?
-Tell me.
-Sorry.
Don't you want to see the dances?
For the past two months I've been
doing nothing but watching dances.
I haven't seen Nandini's dance yet.
And she doesn't know
that I am performing for her.
-Are you serious? Solo dance?
-Yes!
That's great!
Fix your hair.
But will you be able to do it?
Look at your hand.
Bro, I'm the groom. I'll do everything.
Let that be. Leave it like that.
Will you tell me something?
From the back.
-Done?
-Why is it so tight?
-Because you think you're slim.
-Fuck you.
One second. I'll do it.
How did you figure that you wanted
to get married to Nandini? Like...
What's wrong with you?
What a Bollywood like question to ask.
-No, I mean it.
-You and Kavya?
No, I mean, no, not like "no", but...
-We're not thinking about it.
-You can tell me.
Of course I can. But I'm just asking.
How did you know Nandini was the one?
We couldn't find a house
after looking for three months.
-Are you fucking serious?
-No, of course not.
I mean, that was
one of the reasons. But...
I don't know. It wasn't that...
It wasn't anything major, dude.
I mean, the day I thought of it,
I was just... fine.
When I wanted to ask
that girl in the eight grade,
"Will you be my friend?"
I was freaking out more then.
With Nadidni it was... What will happen
after marriage, dude? You know?
And when I thought of like,
"Why Nandini?"
I was like, "I can talk to her."
Whenever, wherever,  whatever.
I mean, even if I am fighting with her,
I can talk to her. You know?
And that makes it...
very sacred.
It's Nandini, man. And it's me.
It's Aakask and Nandini.
It's fun. It's the best.
Finally.
What are you doing?
Why are you taking it off?
What the fuck are you doing?
You arm will get worse.
-It won't. Just...
-Are you sure?
-How else will I wear the coat?
-Okay, all right. Yeah.
Take it off.
-Briyani?
-Yep. Briyani.
How did you get it?
I just realized...
that if I can't keep my Kavu happy,
at least I can try to keep
my biryani monster happy.
But dinner is not even served yet.
How did you manage?
I'm the groom's friend,
everything is possible.
Is it nice?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Even I am sorry.
I mean it, okay?
Even I mean it.
-Are you crying?
-What? No!
I know you were, though.
I felt like crap. Really.
And you should.
The tie has worked wonders.
Full on, bro!
-But besides that, we need to talk.
-Yeah.
We need to.
We don't need to talk right now,
we can talk later.
Listen.
Can you take the day off tomorrow?
-I already did.
-What?
Really?
What else do you think
I was doing on the phone right now?
-You turned out to be pretty smart.
-You've got a gem of a girl.
Kavu? Party animal?
I'm dead.
You're alive.
-Why would you do that?
-Take this. For the hangover.
Thanks.
Where are we?
Forget that.
-Here, a souvenir.
-Thank you.
-How come we're at Sula, though?
-Just...
I was getting a feeling
that we are forgetting ourselves.
And you may know this already.
It's good to come back to familiar places,
because those places help you
remember who you really are.
And you are right.
I am a little disorganized.
And I don't know why
but I can't look at the bigger picture.
I'm selfish as well.
Look, I know
I have been preoccupied and
I have been juggling 100 things
at the same time.
So obviously I mess up
with a thing or two.
But somehow the thing
just ends up being about us.
And...
why do you think that's the case?
Because I take us for granted.
I know I do, I...
I know I shouldn't, but I do.
Last night was really uncomfortable.
I know, but...
comfort comes from
uncomfortable things.
You know, yesterday, after the fight
when I saw you sitting there,
I didn't see this curly-haired girl
with kohl just sitting there,
I saw you.
And I saw you after a very,
very long time.
You know, I really love you, man.
Genuinely.
I don't know.
I had a weird pain in my stomach...
and I don't ever want
to feel that again.
You know, Dhruv?
It's really important for me
to work hard, be independent.
Be self-sufficient.
And it's not about me wanting something
or not wanting something,
or bathing with a bucket and a mug.
It's... it's much more than that.
-I know that.
-No. I don't think you do.
I know it seems obvious, but...
I don't think you really know
where I'm coming from.
My parents never stopped me
from doing anything.
They always taught me to excel in
everything I do.
They always taught me
to be self-sufficient.
Honestly, Kavu, it's never been
my intention to stop you.
No, I know, Dhruv. I...
I'm not saying that. I'm just...
I'm just telling you
where I am coming from.
I'm also figuring this out as we go along.
I just need your support
with whatever I decide.
What happened?
I am suddenly thinking how different
my childhood was.
So, very early in life my parents figured
out that this boy has brains.
So throughout my schooling life,
they pushed me to work harder and harder.
When I entered college, I realized,
fuck, I didn't really have a childhood.
Then I was like, "Now I have to have fun."
And trust me when I say this,
I'm not making excuses,
but I wasn't enjoying my PhD.
Of course, it was fun at the start,
that's why I did it.
But... It was...
I'm not unambitious it's just...
I wasn't liking it.
It just felt like school,
it felt like my job,
It just felt like...
"What? This is all there is?"
Yeah, but anyway,
now it's all about living a life
with a pace I can control myself.
That's not how it works.
It's not that easy when you're
living in the real world, Dhruv.
I know where you are coming from.
I hear you. And...
I need to start caring about this, too,
instead of just thinking about the future.
And I will.
Dhruv, there is one more thing, and I...
I just want you to agree with me,
irrespective of whatever happens.
I want to help you with your family loan.
-Yes, but the thing is--
-Dhruv.
Okay, fine.
Thank you.
No. Thank you.
Fuck, dude.
We've started talking about those things.
Life over career, career over life.
-Why does everything seem so cliché?
-Because it is cliché.
You were right when you say
we are not extraordinary people.
We have to, in fact, work extra hard
to make our every day special.
So, we'll do that, right?
Dhruv?
Do you realize we both look at the world
so differently?
It's not going to be easy, but...
we have to keep at it, right?
What's this?
Is it milk?
It smells weird.
I think the neighboring lady
made something.
You've did this, right?
Mutton cutlet?
I mean, seriously?
Like, where is this from?
-From Moonlight, Momo.
-What?
But how? Like, they don't deliver, dude.
-I know.
-What do you mean I know? Tell me!
I called the owner, I requested him.
He cooked it at home,
and his boy delivered it.
Why don't I feel like crying?
How is it?
I think it's gone bad.
What happened? It's okay.
This could have been perfect, no?
Why are you sad? We can try
that new Chinese place, no?
Let's go.
It's not supposed to be perfect.
It's just supposed to be us, right?
Let's go or it will close. Then we'll
come back and I will have to make Maggi.
-What about scrambled eggs?
-I'll have to make that, too.
-Right.
-Let's go.
-I cook, too, you know.
-Yes, bread and butter.
Shut up! Have you never eaten
anything I cooked?
We had that chili...
What recipe is that?