Kavu. Kavu.
Please get up and close the door,
-I have to go.
-Don't go!
-Come here.
-Kavu, please get up.
I need to eat those bhajjis.
Please get up, Kavu.
-Okay, okay.
-Please get up, get up.
Okay, wear your shoes, I'll just get up,
but you come here for two minutes.
Momo, wait! I'll also come.
You have 90 seconds. Hurry up.
-You called the cab over here?
-No cab today.
-You bought a car?
-Obviously.
We're going to eat bhajjis.
It's not like we'll take the train.
-Be serious.
-It's Aakash's brother's car.
I borrowed it for a day.
Come, it'll be a nice drive.
Yeah! I can sleep now.
Seriously?
Sir, do you know if there's a lady
that sells bhajjis out here?
She sits a little ahead.
-How far?
-Just a little further down.
-You sure?
-Yeah, sure.
Fuck this, man.
Well, thank you.
What's the scene?
She hasn't come since the past few days.
Why?
'Cause her son had a baby,
so she had to go to the village.
Damn it, man.
I can't even be angry at this.
Let's go back.
Back?
Dhruv, we've come all the way here
and look at the view!
How can we just go back?
Are you allergic
to pure oxygen or something?
Oxygen.
I'm taking it to go.
You should get some, too.
Come on, let's go back, man.
Dude, is that a vineyard?
-So?
-So, let's go!
Kavu, let's go.
We'll get in a mess unnecessarily.
I'm sure this qualifies as trespassing.
Hey, relax. It's exciting!
No, Kavu, let's go back, man.
Hey, but it's not like we're doing
anything to these grapes.
-Dude, look!
-No, dude, don't.
No, don't do that, man.
No, Kavu! What is this?
Interesting.
I think they make Chardonnay out of these.
-Yeah?
-You wanna eat?
Eat.
Dude, stop being on your phone.
I'm checking to see if Sturridge
is fit to play or not.
At least don't do it here, no?
It's criminal.
Kavya, you know this place
is just two hours away from Bombay,
and you can come here
any time of the week that you want to,
but, yeah, you are a sloth bear,
so hence, things like these--
Shut up.
It's very difficult
to be in my shoes, okay?
I love my sleep. You don't know how--
Excuse me, sir. Have you come from Bombay?
Yeah, I'm sorry, man. We were just--
Your group's wine tasting session
is about to begin.
You can join the rest of them
at the wine cellar in the basement, sir.
We're not with the group though,
but how much is it for?
-It's for 250 rupees.
-Cool.
Actually, if you have the Little App,
you can do it for 200 rupees.
-Yeah, even better.
-Let's go.
So, wine tasting is all about three S's.
Smell, swirl, and sip.
Now, in the first step,
actually try to put your nose
into the glass and smell the wine.
Now, this particular wine
is called a rosé,
and the salmon pink color
is because of the pressure that we put
on the seed, the juice, and the skin.
In the second step, the swirl,
move your glass like this.
In this, we give the wine some oxygen
to open up and breathe.
Now smell the wine again.
You may notice some difference.
It might smell a bit different.
-It smells much sweeter.
-Yes, it is, sir.
-Cheers.
-Yeah, it does.
Now in the third step, the sip,
actually try taking the sip of wine
and try to gargle it in your mouth,
like this:
This process is called aeration.
In this, we provide the wine
with more oxygen to breathe.
You're so happy you're getting
to do this in public.
What is this?
Sir, don't worry.
I'll get you a napkin, sir.
This is no way to behave! Be serious!
I'm sorry.
Wine tasting is an art
to be savored drop by drop,
bit by bit, sip by sip.
I can't believe we came here
to eat bhajjis.
By the way, that handloom exhibition's
happening today.
Remember to message auntie.
You message her?
Then don't get pissed off
when I take out my phone.
So funny.
Dhruv.
I've been thinking. Should I quit my job?
What?
Careful.
-Are you drunk?
-Yeah.
No, I've just not been enjoying it
for a while now.
I know. I could see that.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I knew you would say it yourself,
and you did.
In fact, consumer studies...
this theory called revealed preferences.
It basically means your actions reveal
what you want.
How cool is that?
But it's scary, no?
What if I quit my job
and never figure out what I wanna do?
Okay, so let's assume you quit your job.
And say there's a 50 percent chance
that when you quit--
No, Dhruv.
Please don't talk in terms of probability.
Just talk simply.
If you quit to figure out
what you want to do,
then it's not a waste of time. Simple.
Pros and cons.
Yes, let's do pros and cons.
Let's be a little serious.
Pros first or cons?
-Cons.
-Okay.
So, you won't be earning anything.
You may run out of your savings.
Your parents may not understand
your decision at first.
Everybody around you
would be getting richer.
Some lifestyle changes,
even though I'm there, but still.
It may not look good on your CV.
It could take a while
before you find your next job.
You could just be more confused
after this.
Okay, that's enough. That's enough.
Pros now.
Pros, pros, pros.
Hey!
I'm thinking.
It takes time.
Yeah. The break may help you realize
whether you want to continue
working in sales
or some other department...
Or just-- Just explore
a totally different career path.
Like becoming a dog babysitter.
-How cool is that?
-That is actually cool.
-And it's a thing, you know? Dogsitter.
-Dogsitter.
Anyway, focus. Okay.
So, yeah, you could travel.
You could read more.
You could paint more. You could draw more.
You can just explore yourself, you know?
Just do new things. Grow.
-Now you're just repeating yourself.
-You figured it out.
Anyway, so there are more cons than pros.
Yeah, but I like the pros better.
I think I'm seriously
gonna think about it.
So, it's true, huh?
When you come to a place like this,
with good pure oxygen,
it really cleanses your mind.
You get clarity.
I'm taking credit for all of this,
by the way.
Really?
You wanted to go back two hours ago.
-Yeah, but--
-And I spotted this place.
But we came here because of me.
It's not about this place, anyway.
I was fine until I saw that video
you shared on Facebook about that girl.
-Which one?
-The Bangalore girl.
-The poem, right?
-Yeah.
About what it feels like
to be an introvert,
and it's not because I am
an introvert or anything.
It's just that I really like the way
she expressed herself, you know?
I wonder if I have ever expressed myself
so well.
You must have.
I don't know.
Maybe I did when I was a kid.
It all reduced when I grew up.
I used to concentrate so much
when I used to paint.
I used to be really active in school,
you know?
Debate clubs and cultural events.
I used to be on the top of my game
all the time.
I really enjoyed being busy and tired.
You know, I thought, when I'd grow up,
I'll do something kick-ass.
I've not done anything of that sort yet.
And I loved surprising myself.
I don't remember
the last time that it's happened.
I think I have just become very...
you know, comfortable.
-Very--
-Lazy?
Not lazy.
Fine. Lazy.
I hate that word...
and I've not only become lazy physically,
but mentally, also.
Don't take this in the wrong way,
but... most of the things that we do
are the things that you want to do.
-What?
-And I love doing them,
but it's just that, honestly,
it takes more effort from my side
to travel two hours
to eat some bhajjis or cutlets--
What? Wait.
So you're not here to have some bhajjis?
-Of course not.
-Hey.
I came here for us.
We've not been out of the city
for a long time,
and... there's another reason
which I'll tell you about later.
Well, okay.
At least you're thinking about all this.
You just have to figure out
a few things and...
This is good.
This is a step in the right direction.
Sounding very formal right now.
Yeah, because I'm being serious.
Like serious, like, you know?
-Serious, like serious!
-Yeah, yeah, got it.
I'll seriously think about it.
You didn't feel bad
about what I said, right?
Are you crazy?
So nice you're opening up and talking
about things that you're feeling.
It's good. See, all this is nice.
Every time we go out, we have fun.
We should just do this more often.
I know.
It's funny how so many girls my age
are busy getting married and traveling
and doing so well in their careers,
and here I am planning to quit my job
and start something completely new.
I don't even know what.
You're just figuring out how to make
your everyday life more fun and better.
Not many people think like that,
Kavya Kulkarni, so this is nice.
-Chill.
-That's true.
And dog babysitter
is actually a good plan.
Dogsitter. What's dog babysitter?
Yeah, same thing.
Now say,
"Thank you, Dhanush."
Thank you, Dhruv.
Wow, manners! Where did that come from?
That's because
I'm feeling really light right now.
I don't want to go back to Mumbai.
Like, seriously.
You mean, "Seriously!"
I didn't come here for you, silly.
I came here because...
Do you see that?
Pretty, dude. Looking nice.
You don't remember, do you?
Exactly two years ago
is when we met for the first time.
No.
Let me check. I don't think it's today.
I think it's tomorrow. See? It's tomorrow.
It's today. You want to bet?
No, I have the tickets. Let's do this.
Loser.
-It's today.
-Right.
When did you change my status to,
"Girls, be careful. The Don is here"?
When you were having a shower.
-Which one's mine?
-Here.
Take either one.
I told you to make mine
with more milk and less sugar, no?
Which one are you reading?
This is the one with...
Just stop here for a second.
-Hey, you want to take this one?
-No, thanks.
Are you sure? I can take another one.
Okay.
-Hey, where are you headed?
-Powai.
Cool, I'm going there, too.
Let me drop you.
-Sure?
-Yeah.
-Can I please use your bathroom?
-What?
I have lizards in mine
and I'm really scared of them.
Hey, what? I can't use
a nice-smelling fruity shower gel?
No, of course. Of course you can.
Do you want some green tea?
I make really nice green tea.
Sure.