What do you think?
Don't take a picture.
I've not draped it properly.
You look so beautiful.
When did you buy that nose thingy?
It's a nath, Dhruv.
It's a Maharashtrian design.
Remember I told you
I was saving up for it?
I bought it a couple of weeks back
from VelvetCase.
Something like that would make
anyone look pretty, no?
Thanks, Dhruv. How charming.
Anyway, I don't think it goes
with this sari.
And this sari is also
not a very wedding-type.
-I think I'm gonna try something new.
-Kavu. Please hurry up, man.
We have to be up at 4 a.m. and leave.
And that bhajji lady
sits only for three hours--
Just give me two minutes. I'll be back.
What do you think of this?
It's nice.
See, I like this but somehow--
Dhruv.
It's nice.
Okay, last one.
Dhruv.
It's nice.
Stop saying "it's nice" to everything.
Say something different.
Hey, because it's just nice,
it's not amazing. It's too late.
My mind is not working.
Kavu, let's go to bed. We have to get
up at 4 a.m. and travel for two hours.
I really want to eat those corn bhajjis.
None of these are amazing,
and they're not going well with the nath.
I think I'll buy something nice
for Prachi's wedding.
-I'll come in two minutes. You sleep.
-Good night.
Good night.
Wake up, Momo.
-Wake up.
-Let me sleep two minutes.
It's 12:30, Dhruv.
What?
Shit, we missed it.
What the hell, man!
-You forgot to put the alarm?
-Because of the whole sari thing, no?
Hey, how is it my fault?
Don't turn this around me.
You forgot to put the alarm.
Yeah, because I was sleepy and confused.
Yeah, it's okay!
No. I really wanted
to eat those bhajjis, man.
We've lost half a day.
Everyone else is having so much fun.
-We're sitting here in bed and--
-We were supposed to have a good time.
But what is the point of us fighting now?
I know how to turn this Sunday around.
Give me 30 minutes,
and I'll fix something for you.
Son of a bitch.
Kavu, we have to check
this new Kerala place out.
It looks kick-ass.
Shit. It's not possible, no?
At least appreciate the effort, Dhruv.
That I'll obviously do. But Bombay Bhukkad
put up this new post and I thought,
"let's eat something new today."
So, I couldn't help
but fantasize about food.
One minute! One minute!
Don't do that.
Bacon.
Wait, wait, wait.
What? Please let me eat.
I'm starving.
Please.
Get the mustard first, please.
Such an amazing experience, dude.
-What is?
-Dating a sloth bear like you.
-I'm not lazy, okay?
-Of course, no. Yeah. Sure.
-I'm just chilled out.
-Of course.
I made all this.
I know, and it looks great.
I mean it. Thank you.
Dude, this Megha keeps traveling
all the time, man.
It's not fair. She even went
to a Coldplay concert. Look.
Show?
Cool, man. Hey, how come we
don't have a Pokémon at home?
Viraj found two, you know?
Not fair.
Okay, listen. Let's watch a film.
Oh, it's my turn, no?
No. My turn.
Shit, you remember.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
Inside Out.
No! No, no, no.
Hey, what's your problem?
I heard it's a good film.
Yeah, it's a very good film.
But it's an animated film.
Those films have at least two,
three moments which will make you cry.
Then you'll get sentimental
and will stop talking.
Then I will keep asking,
"Kavu, what happened?"
"Do you want to talk?"
But you wouldn't want to talk.
But exactly at 7:00
you would want to talk,
and that's when Liverpool
will be playing Chelsea.
And then you'll make a face.
You make exactly this face.
Yes. This face. Hold, hold.
So pretty when pissed off.
Bing Bong.
You made it!
-You okay?
-Yeah, obviously.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
Oh, so cute. You cried and all.
This is why I didn't want
to watch this film.
Aakash is chilling in Goa
drinking beer at the beach.
And I'm sitting here mourning Bing Bong.
Don't ruin the film like that.
It's a good film.
I know, but I just wanted to watch
something nice, relaxed, funny.
Want to go to the arcade
and play air hockey?
Been a while
since I kicked your ass at it.
No way. Liverpool versus Chelsea, 7 p.m.
Hey, so what? One game.
Come on!
Chicken.
-Okay, fine. One game. We'll be back by 7.
-Sure, you're on.
-You should not wear kohl on Sundays.
-Just like you don't shower on Sundays.
Exactly. At least once a week
we should know how we really look.
I think it's quite nice and intense.
It's very naked, no?
You talking to me?
Taxi Driver, like, so obvious.
Excuse me, sir.
If you don't mind me asking,
-where are you going?
-To play games.
-Arcade, Dhruv.
-Yeah, arcade.
-You can't go in.
-Why? What's the scene? Who are you?
Actually, I'm the manager
of this mall, sir.
There's a kid's birthday party upstairs.
And your T-shirt reads
"In Cock We Trust."
Yeah, so?
Sir, someone might file a complaint.
It could become an issue.
Please understand.
The T-shirt is referencing
my favorite chili sauce.
Sriracha is a name of a sauce, sir.
That doesn't matter, ma'am.
If someone complains it will be a problem.
Plus, today is my first day.
Don't talk rubbish.
We want to play games, just let us in.
Try and understand, sir.
There could be a problem.
Someone could file a complaint.
-It would put my job at risk.
-How can you do this?
Please, please cooperate.
This is unacceptable!
Thank you so much, sir.
Thank you, thank you. Sorry.
Please come again tomorrow! Thank you!
How could he throw us out?
You should have taken a shower,
changed your T-shirt.
Today is a Sunday.
I don't bathe on Sundays.
-You know it.
-So, what do you wanna do now?
I don't know. Do you wanna
just go home and have sex?
At least don't look this bored
while saying it.
Then what should we do?
-Do you want to go to a salon with me?
-What? Why would I want to do that?
Because then I can get a hair spa,
and when you play with my hair,
it'll be more fun.
When was the last time I did that?
If I put my hand in there,
it'll get lost in there.
But you used to. And I miss all that.
-But I have a match.
-So, watch it on your phone.
Please.
I've decided. We're going to a salon,
and I'm buying a coupon on Little App.
We are not going.
-Don't buy coupons, you'll waste money.
-That won't happen.
I'll get a full refund.
That's not the point. It's Sunday.
-Just watch it on your phone.
-It's not the same thing!
Okay, see. There are 52 Sundays in a year,
amongst them, the chances of Liverpool--
I know, the chances of Liverpool
playing on a Sunday is 8.8 percent.
-Yeah.
-But it's a Sunday. I wanna do something.
Pretty curls.
But why don't you maintain your curls?
-That would be nice.
-I don't know how to.
Why don't you do any protein treatment
or any kind of styling for your hair?
-Listen.
-Yeah?
Should I get the hair spa done
or a keratin treatment?
-If I get the keratin--
-Shit.
It was so close, man.
Yeah, get it done.
Which one?
-Get the herbal one.
-Why not the extra protein one?
Get that. That's the best one.
You just watch your game.
You do what you think is best.
-Okay.
-Yeah? Yeah.
Fuck! Shit!
Costa! You son of a bitch!
Rascal! You swine! Dick! Son of a bitch!
-You need to talk to him.
-Yeah.
Could you please watch your match outside?
Sister fucker!
How's it looking?
What did you do?
I can't tell the difference.
Just like there's no difference
in Liverpool's position in the league?
Why are you getting angry?
You need to learn how to behave in public.
-It was a mistake, man.
-A mistake?
Really?
This was seriously by mistake.
Seriously.
Want to grab some dinner?
Chinese?
Mughlai?
It's too oily.
Italian?
Too boring.
Mexican?
Actually, I'm done.
Don't say that, man.
Hey, I'm full, but I'll have a little bit.
Promise.
Hey, let's go to that Kerala place.
Oh, yeah. How did I forget about that?
Good one, Kulkarni.
Always.
Forty-five minutes waiting.
Serious?
You know what? Let's go home.
Pick ingredients for Thai curry.
We'll have that with rice.
Best option.
Oh, yeah.
I can make a full Snap story
with instructions
on how to make Thai curry.
Screw you, Megha.
Kavu, your day was nothing
like how you made it out on Snapchat.
Yeah, so what?
I don't wanna tell everyone
that I had a boring Sunday.
Everyone is going out to places and we're
sitting here doing what, I don't know.
What's this solid FOMO?
I know our day didn't go
according to the plan,
but it's not that we had
that bad a Sunday.
We had an epic breakfast.
Dude, I got chucked out of a salon.
Like, how often does that happen?
We'll be laughing about it for two months.
And seeing you
with those funny red hair clips,
and watching Coutinho score that goal,
now, that made my Sunday.
Of course, it could be much cooler
and much happening
but that can happen
on any other day, can't it?
And we still have to make that Thai curry!
Listen.
Can we just order pizza instead?
I am really tired.
Thank God you said that.
Even I'm very tired, man.
Wait, what about your Snap story, then?
I don't care.
-Yeah?
-Really.
-And what will people say?
-Other people can go to hell!
You know, it might sound lame,
but you know what I really want to do?
I want to have some pizza,
have a nice glass of red wine,
finish watching Inside Out,
and sleep.
That sounds perfect.
Sounds like our kind of Sunday.
Exactly.
DHRUV: WHEN DID IT BECOME AVAILABLE?