Dude, you turned out to be
Santa Claus, man!
Where are you, bro?
What is this, Kavu?
Okay, please wrap up quickly.
I'm starving.
Yeah, I'm waiting downstairs.
Get here quickly. Yup.
Yes, dude, where are you?
Yes, just come straight down.
Straight, straight.
It left! He's not going to wait that long.
Where are you?
Yeah, you can see paan shop?
Take a left from there!
What do you see? No, man. Not the temple.
Where is this guy?
He's right there, Dhruv!
Okay, you've reached the spot.
Just stay where you are.
No, we don't need this.
-Just get us two mutton cutlet-gravy--
-Just one.
We'll share, won't we?
-Bring it with bread on the side.
-The mutton cutlet gravy is over.
Can you check again?
I'm sure you'll find one piece.
I've checked it thoroughly,
and it's not there.
-Can you go ask once again?
-I'm telling you, I checked everything.
Sir, we've come here from very far.
Please go and take a look.
If you want anything else tell me.
Bring two mutton biryanis.
-Just one.
-What?
-Just get one mutton biryani.
-Two or one?
Just one.
One?
I haven't eaten since morning.
I only ate biscuits with the hope
of having mutton cutlet gravy.
That's also over.
Are you kidding?
You should have come earlier.
Everything is over by this hour.
Okay, get us the best thing
that's available at this hour.
-So, I'll bring scrambled eggs and bread.
-Wow, scrambled eggs and bread!
So, I took a two-hour trip
to eat scrambled eggs and bread?
Just relax.
-Make a four egg scramble.
-Four egg scramble?
Who eats a four egg scramble?
You eat it, Dhruv.
How can I eat a four egg scramble?
No, get a two egg scramble.
-Four eggs or two?
-Sir, just two eggs.
You forgot and you already ate.
What's the point of coming today?
What's with the formality?
Bro, add a caramel custard to the bill.
Not available.
Where are the cabs?
Over there.
Finally found a cab.
Sir, please drop us to Powai.
No, dude. I'm not going.
I wanna go home and
watch the new episode of Game of Thrones.
We can watch it tomorrow, Dhruv.
-We decided five days ago!
-I don't have a calendar fixed in my mind.
Don't say things for the sake of it!
and haven't watched a single scene!
-I bought popcorn.
-Guys, get off and fight!
Have some shame!
Shame? Why are you being such a mom?
Dude, don't say emo stuff like that!
It fucks with my head.
Please, Kavu, there's still time.
We can still get out of here.
Is there more?
Go on, dude. Have some.
-I don't eat this.
-It's awesome.
Kavu. Where are you?
Crazy girl. You're up to no good.
He's an ass.
Now, who is this Asif?
It was amazing.
Potato.
Loose motions.
Come on, it's just a game.
Is that right?
What do you think?
You'll do this all by yourself?
Who are you checking out?
Look at her.
But how could they let Hodor die?
I told you this will happen at the party.
But it didn't happen at the party,
we found out in the lift!
What the hell, man!
And I have this coupon from Little App.
All right. I'll bring it.
-Say.
-Yeah, there's Liverpool over there.
Chicken shawarma.
They've made it so well! Full power.
So, I figured,
And anyway,
Is that so?
You were making such a fuss
before getting there.